NGUYEN VAN KHANH

0835772195 nguyenkhanhlhp1@gmail.com DOB: 15/10/1997

FrontEnd Developer

OBJECTIVE

I am a Front-End developer 4 years of experience. Skill in cross-browser web developer, clean coding. I always try to create website interface with meticulousness and good performance. React is the framework I have the most experience with about 4 years.

EDUCATION

Hanoi University of Science and Technology

09/2015 - 06/2020

Major: computer engineering

SKILLS

Technologies HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React JS

Frameworks, Libraries Material UI, Redux Toolkit, Redux Saga, React query,

Socket

Other Git, Align scrum

EXPERIENCE

Work in Advesa Digital Solutions

01/2021 - Now

Sale eCommerce Management System (4 member)

Bring data-driven suite of tools is designed to help supercharge your business. Deliver personalized, omnichannel experiences that your customers expect, the smart way.

Technologies: ReactJS, Redux, Redux Saga, Material UI.

My responsibility was to build interface of this web app.

Live chatbot Management System (4 member)

live chatbot with a human touch, empowering businesses to provide personalized experiences at scale, management for administrators with features such as live chat, all chat, vistor tracking, analytics,...

Technologies: ReactJS, React query, Material UI, TypeScript, Socket.

My responsibility was to build interface of this web app.

Work in SAPO 04/2019 – 12/2020

Sales POS software Sapo (3 member)

brings businesses, retail shop owners an overall sales and management platform from offline to online

Technologies: ReactJS, Redux, Redux persist, Hooks, Material UI.

My responsibility was to build interface of this web app.

Building the sales management system Sapo (5 member)

Building the SAPO sales management system using react technology

Technologies: ReactJS, Redux toolkit, Redux persist, Hooks, Material UI.

My responsibility was to create interface modules.

Work as internship in NTT DATA Corporation

01/2019 - 03/2019

Library management project (4 member)

Building a library management system for Japan

Technologies: JavaScript, ReactJS, bootstrap, cypress.

My responsibility was to build interface and automatic test of this web app.

HOBBIES

Reading books

Running

Coffee meet friends